[
    {"id": 1, "front": "1", "back": {"name": "واحد", "soundsLike": "waḥid", "translation": "One"}},
    {"id": 2, "front": "2", "back": {"name": "اتنين", "soundsLike": "itnayn", "translation": "Two"}},
    {"id": 3, "front": "3", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة", "soundsLike": "thalātha", "translation": "Three"}},
    {"id": 4, "front": "4", "back": {"name": "أربعة", "soundsLike": "arba'a", "translation": "Four"}},
    {"id": 5, "front": "5", "back": {"name": "خمسة", "soundsLike": "khamsa", "translation": "Five"}},
    {"id": 6, "front": "6", "back": {"name": "ستة", "soundsLike": "sitta", "translation": "Six"}},
    {"id": 7, "front": "7", "back": {"name": "سبعة", "soundsLike": "sab'a", "translation": "Seven"}},
    {"id": 8, "front": "8", "back": {"name": "ثمانية", "soundsLike": "thamāniya", "translation": "Eight"}},
    {"id": 9, "front": "9", "back": {"name": "تسعة", "soundsLike": "tis'a", "translation": "Nine"}},
    {"id": 10, "front": "10", "back": {"name": "عشرة", "soundsLike": "ʿashara", "translation": "Ten"}},

    {"id": 11, "front": "11", "back": {"name": "أحد عشر", "soundsLike": "aḥad ʿashar", "translation": "Eleven"}},
    {"id": 12, "front": "12", "back": {"name": "اثنا عشر", "soundsLike": "ithnā ʿashar", "translation": "Twelve"}},
    {"id": 13, "front": "13", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة عشر", "soundsLike": "thalātha ʿashar", "translation": "Thirteen"}},
    {"id": 14, "front": "14", "back": {"name": "أربعة عشر", "soundsLike": "arba'a ʿashar", "translation": "Fourteen"}},
    {"id": 15, "front": "15", "back": {"name": "خمسة عشر", "soundsLike": "khamsa ʿashar", "translation": "Fifteen"}},
    {"id": 16, "front": "16", "back": {"name": "ستة عشر", "soundsLike": "sitta ʿashar", "translation": "Sixteen"}},
    {"id": 17, "front": "17", "back": {"name": "سبعة عشر", "soundsLike": "sab'a ʿashar", "translation": "Seventeen"}},
    {"id": 18, "front": "18", "back": {"name": "ثمانية عشر", "soundsLike": "thamāniya ʿashar", "translation": "Eighteen"}},
    {"id": 19, "front": "19", "back": {"name": "تسعة عشر", "soundsLike": "tis'a ʿashar", "translation": "Nineteen"}},
    {"id": 20, "front": "20", "back": {"name": "عشرون", "soundsLike": "ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty"}},

    {"id": 21, "front": "21", "back": {"name": "واحد وعشرون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-one"}},
    {"id": 22, "front": "22", "back": {"name": "اثنان وعشرون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-two"}},
    {"id": 23, "front": "23", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-three"}},
    {"id": 24, "front": "24", "back": {"name": "أربعة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-four"}},
    {"id": 25, "front": "25", "back": {"name": "خمسة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-five"}},
    {"id": 26, "front": "26", "back": {"name": "ستة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-six"}},
    {"id": 27, "front": "27", "back": {"name": "سبعة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-seven"}},
    {"id": 28, "front": "28", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وعشرون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-eight"}},
    {"id": 29, "front": "29", "back": {"name": "تسعة وعشرون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-ʿishrūn", "translation": "Twenty-nine"}},
    {"id": 30, "front": "30", "back": {"name": "ثلاثون", "soundsLike": "thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty"}},

    {"id": 31, "front": "31", "back": {"name": "واحد وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-one"}},
    {"id": 32, "front": "32", "back": {"name": "اثنان وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-two"}},
    {"id": 33, "front": "33", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-three"}},
    {"id": 34, "front": "34", "back": {"name": "أربعة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-four"}},
    {"id": 35, "front": "35", "back": {"name": "خمسة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-five"}},
    {"id": 36, "front": "36", "back": {"name": "ستة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-six"}},
    {"id": 37, "front": "37", "back": {"name": "سبعة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-seven"}},
    {"id": 38, "front": "38", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-eight"}},
    {"id": 39, "front": "39", "back": {"name": "تسعة وثلاثون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-thalāthūn", "translation": "Thirty-nine"}},
    {"id": 40, "front": "40", "back": {"name": "أربعون", "soundsLike": "arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty"}},

    {"id": 41, "front": "41", "back": {"name": "واحد وأربعون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-one"}},
    {"id": 42, "front": "42", "back": {"name": "اثنان وأربعون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-two"}},
    {"id": 43, "front": "43", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-three"}},
    {"id": 44, "front": "44", "back": {"name": "أربعة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-four"}},
    {"id": 45, "front": "45", "back": {"name": "خمسة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-five"}},
    {"id": 46, "front": "46", "back": {"name": "ستة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-six"}},
    {"id": 47, "front": "47", "back": {"name": "سبعة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-seven"}},
    {"id": 48, "front": "48", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وأربعون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-eight"}},
    {"id": 49, "front": "49", "back": {"name": "تسعة وأربعون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-arba'ūn", "translation": "Forty-nine"}},
    {"id": 50, "front": "50", "back": {"name": "خمسون", "soundsLike": "khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty"}},

    {"id": 51, "front": "51", "back": {"name": "واحد وخمسون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-one"}},
    {"id": 52, "front": "52", "back": {"name": "اثنان وخمسون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-two"}},
    {"id": 53, "front": "53", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-three"}},
    {"id": 54, "front": "54", "back": {"name": "أربعة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-four"}},
    {"id": 55, "front": "55", "back": {"name": "خمسة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-five"}},
    {"id": 56, "front": "56", "back": {"name": "ستة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-six"}},
    {"id": 57, "front": "57", "back": {"name": "سبعة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-seven"}},
    {"id": 58, "front": "58", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وخمسون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-eight"}},
    {"id": 59, "front": "59", "back": {"name": "تسعة وخمسون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-khamsūn", "translation": "Fifty-nine"}},
    {"id": 60, "front": "60", "back": {"name": "ستون", "soundsLike": "sittūn", "translation": "Sixty"}},

    {"id": 61, "front": "61", "back": {"name": "واحد وستون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-one"}},
    {"id": 62, "front": "62", "back": {"name": "اثنان وستون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-two"}},
    {"id": 63, "front": "63", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وستون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-three"}},
    {"id": 64, "front": "64", "back": {"name": "أربعة وستون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-four"}},
    {"id": 65, "front": "65", "back": {"name": "خمسة وستون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-five"}},
    {"id": 66, "front": "66", "back": {"name": "ستة وستون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-six"}},
    {"id": 67, "front": "67", "back": {"name": "سبعة وستون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-seven"}},
    {"id": 68, "front": "68", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وستون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-eight"}},
    {"id": 69, "front": "69", "back": {"name": "تسعة وستون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-sittūn", "translation": "Sixty-nine"}},
    {"id": 70, "front": "70", "back": {"name": "سبعون", "soundsLike": "sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy"}},

    {"id": 71, "front": "71", "back": {"name": "واحد وسبعون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-one"}},
    {"id": 72, "front": "72", "back": {"name": "اثنان وسبعون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-two"}},
    {"id": 73, "front": "73", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-three"}},
    {"id": 74, "front": "74", "back": {"name": "أربعة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-four"}},
    {"id": 75, "front": "75", "back": {"name": "خمسة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-five"}},
    {"id": 76, "front": "76", "back": {"name": "ستة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-six"}},
    {"id": 77, "front": "77", "back": {"name": "سبعة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-seven"}},
    {"id": 78, "front": "78", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وسبعون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-eight"}},
    {"id": 79, "front": "79", "back": {"name": "تسعة وسبعون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-sab'ūn", "translation": "Seventy-nine"}},
    {"id": 80, "front": "80", "back": {"name": "ثمانون", "soundsLike": "thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty"}},

    {"id": 81, "front": "81", "back": {"name": "واحد وثمانون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-one"}},
    {"id": 82, "front": "82", "back": {"name": "اثنان وثمانون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-two"}},
    {"id": 83, "front": "83", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-three"}},
    {"id": 84, "front": "84", "back": {"name": "أربعة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-four"}},
    {"id": 85, "front": "85", "back": {"name": "خمسة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-five"}},
    {"id": 86, "front": "86", "back": {"name": "ستة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-six"}},
    {"id": 87, "front": "87", "back": {"name": "سبعة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-seven"}},
    {"id": 88, "front": "88", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وثمانون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-eight"}},
    {"id": 89, "front": "89", "back": {"name": "تسعة وثمانون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-thamānūn", "translation": "Eighty-nine"}},
    {"id": 90, "front": "90", "back": {"name": "تسعون", "soundsLike": "tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety"}},

    {"id": 91, "front": "91", "back": {"name": "واحد وتسعون", "soundsLike": "waḥid wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-one"}},
    {"id": 92, "front": "92", "back": {"name": "اثنان وتسعون", "soundsLike": "ithnān wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-two"}},
    {"id": 93, "front": "93", "back": {"name": "ثلاثة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "thalātha wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-three"}},
    {"id": 94, "front": "94", "back": {"name": "أربعة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "arba'a wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-four"}},
    {"id": 95, "front": "95", "back": {"name": "خمسة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "khamsa wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-five"}},
    {"id": 96, "front": "96", "back": {"name": "ستة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "sitta wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-six"}},
    {"id": 97, "front": "97", "back": {"name": "سبعة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "sab'a wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-seven"}},
    {"id": 98, "front": "98", "back": {"name": "ثمانية وتسعون", "soundsLike": "thamāniya wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-eight"}},
    {"id": 99, "front": "99", "back": {"name": "تسعة وتسعون", "soundsLike": "tis'a wa-tis'ūn", "translation": "Ninety-nine"}},
    {"id": 100, "front": "100", "back": {"name": "مائة", "soundsLike": "mi'a", "translation": "One hundred"}}
]
